Anna Hyatt Huntington Papers
Anna Hyatt Huntington Papers
1887-1973
Huntington, Anna Hyatt, 1876-1973
90 linear ft.
Papers of the American sculptor, specializing in equestrian figures and animals. Correspondence, 1887-1965; diaries, 1925-1958; articles; exhibition catalogs; financial and legal material; manuscripts; and photographs.
146333
Biographical History
Anna Vaughn Hyatt Huntington (1876-1973) was an award-winning American sculptor, best known for her animal pieces and her large equestrian statues.
Born in Cambridge, Mass. on March 10, 1876, the daughter of noted palaeontologist, naturalist, and Harvard professor, Alpheus Hyatt, she had planned to become a concert violinist but was encouraged by her sister to try sculpture. She studied briefly under H.E. Kitsen of Boston, and in the Art Students' League in New York, and received valuable criticism from Gustav Borglum. Other artists with whom she studied include Hermon Atkins MacNeil, George Grey Barnard, Gertrude Vanderbilt Whitney, and Malvina Hoffman.
As early as 1898 she began to exhibit her work and by 1906 had established a reputation as a fine sculptor of animals. She lived in Europe from 1906 to 1908 and again in 1910 when she won an honorable mention for her plaster model of Joan of Arc. She then returned to America where she executed many commissions, several of monumental size, such as the Joan of Arc which was placed along Riverside Drive in New York City.
In 1923 she became the second wife of Archer Milton Huntington, adopted son of Collis P. Huntington who founded the Southern Pacific Railroad. Archer Huntington was vitally interested in art, particularly Spanish art and culture; he encouraged his wife's work and she came to share his love for Spain and its people. Despite a lengthy bout with tuberculosis beginning in 1927, Anna continued to actively produce and show her work after their marriage. In 1937 the Huntingtons moved from New York City to Haverstraw, New York to an estate they called "Rocas," and then in 1940 to an estate and farm near Bethel, Connecticut, which they called "Stanerigg." Here Mrs. Huntington became interested in owning and breeding Scottish deerhounds and her kennel at Stanerigg produced a number of award-winning dogs, but her main focus was always her art. She continued to sculpt and produce fine pieces until illness forced her to stop in 1972, and she died shortly thereafter in 1973.
Sculptors Marjorie Jay Daingerfield and Katherine Ward Lane Weems both studied with her, and she was the friend and collaborator of sculptor Abastenia St. Leger Eberle (whom she affectionately called "Stennie") and a colleague of artist Elizabeth Norton.
Particularly well-known are Mrs. Huntington's heroic equestrian statues. These include El Cid (several locations including the Hispanic Society of America in New York and Seville, Spain), Young Andrew Jackson (Andrew Jackson State Park, Lancaster, South Carolina), General Israel Putnam (Putnam Memorial Park, Redding, Connecticut), and The Torchbearers (Ciudad Universitaria, Madrid). Her last major equestrian piece was a statue of Cuban nationalist José Martí, which stands in New York's Central Park; the piece was begun in the mid 1950s but due to the United States' difficult relations with Cuba it was not unveiled until 1965.
Mrs. Huntington was an active member of the American Academy of Arts and Letters, the National Academy of Design, and the National Sculpture Society, and gave generously to numerous museums, charities and civic organizations. With her husband, she founded Brookgreen Gardens in South Carolina, a state preserve and sculpture garden, and the Mariner's Museum in Newport News, Virginia; the couple also donated 15,000 acres of forestland in the central Adirondacks to the State University of New York College of Environmental Science and Forestry (SUNY-ESF). Mr. Huntington founded the Hispanic Society and Museum in New York City, and Anna also actively supported this organization.
Mrs. Huntington received numerous awards and honors over her career, among them a silver medal at the San Francisco Exposition in 1915, a gold medal in Philadelphia in 1917, and the Saltus Gold Medal from the National Academy of Design. She became a Chevalier of the Legion d'Honneur in 1933, was named "Woman of the Americas" in 1958, and on her ninetieth birthday she received greetings from friends, fellow artists, and admirers worldwide. Her sculpture is in the permanent collections of more than 200 museums across the United States as well as overseas.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Anna Hyatt Huntington Papers include art files, original artwork, biographical material, correspondence-subject files, financial-legal files, memorabilia, photographs, printed material, reference files, and a few writings by others.
Art files contains material relating to Mrs. Huntington's art -- transport, insurance, research material, copyright information, correspondence with bronze foundries, lists of exhibitions, and similar material.
Artwork (original) consists of a few items by Anna (a medal and some sketches) and original artwork by others, primarily sketches, drawings, watercolors, and so on. Original artwork sent with correspondence was kept with it and may be found in the correspondence-subject files under the surname of the correspondent.
Biographical material contains material on the Beebe, Huntington, Hyatt, Mayor, Reynolds, and Vaughn families. (See also Related material, below).
Correspondence-subject files consists of correspondence with, and material related to, various individuals and organizations. The correspondence of Anna's husband, Archer Milton Huntington, has been merged into this series. The files include artists, authors, gallery owners, friends and family, as well as notes from visitors to Brookgreen; art galleries, museums, schools, cities, societies, charities, and so on; and topics ranging from blueprints to maps. Of particular interest in this series are Anna's extensive correspondence with her mother, Audella Hyatt (4 boxes spanning forty years), and her sister, Harriet Hyatt Mayor (2 boxes spanning 60 years). Included also is material relating to Brookgreen Gardens (6 boxes, including annual reports, bank statements, cash statements, a deed, inventories, minutes, photographs, reports, and other material) and the Hispanic Society of America (3 boxes). The 11 boxes of Scottish deerhound material reflect Anna's intense interest in the breed.
Financial-legal files includes bank statements, files on trusts and deeds of gift, and Archer Milton Huntington's financial notebooks; some papers relate to Brookgreen and the Hispanic Society of America, and there are some legal papers relating to Collis P. Huntington's adopted daughter (therefore Archer's adoptive sister) Clara Hatzfeldt.
Memorabilia is extensive and comprises address books, awards and certificates, daily calendars for nearly fifty years, Anna's own diaries (39 volumes covering 1925-1965), membership cards, passports, plaques, more than 25 scrapbooks, and secretary's diaries (1934-1945). Miscellaneous items include Mrs. Huntington's honorary degree from the University of South Carolina and a beautiful framed decree of honorary citizenship from Valencia, Spain.
Photographs includes photographs of artwork (primarily Mrs. Huntington's but a few of others); exhibits; family members and friends; family property (Atalaya, Rocas, Stanerigg, various New York houses); and miscellaneous people (Francisco Franco, Jose Simeon Canas, Robert Peary) and places (Africa, Monaco, Spain, New Orleans, Nashville). Also included here are negatives, slides, photoplates (metal plates affixed to wooden blocks) and three 16mm films. Some correspondence-subject files also contain photographs; these are noted in the inventory below. Of particular interest, in Box 93, is a photograph of a sculpture of a boy and a dog which is annotated on the back as "Anna V. Hyatt and Harriet Randolph Hyatt, only piece done together." According to several sources, this collaboration was Anna's first piece, and its acceptance for exhibition and subsequent purchase encouraged her to give up the violin and turn her talents to sculpture.
Printed material consists of articles (about Anna, about family members, about others); books (about Anna, about others, and one by Archer), clippings (about Anna, about family members, about others); exhibit catalogs; press releases; and miscellaneous advertisements, fliers, magazines, pamphlets, programs, and so on. A few of the magazines are in French or Spanish.
Anna's Reference files contain vast numbers of clippings, photographs, books, and magazines used by Anna as reference for her sculptures.
Writings of others contains typescripts and manuscripts of articles, books, essays, poems, and other pieces. The bulk of the material is that of Emile Schaub-Koch, a French art critic who wrote extensively about Anna and her work. There are also a few poems by Archer Milton Huntington. Some correspondence-subject files also contain original poems, essays, or other writings; these are noted in the inventory below.
Deerhounds (1902-1957, 5 Boxes) were a long-time hobby of Mrs. Huntington. In the early 1930's, she became interested in introducing the breed of Scottish deerhounds into the United States. She maintained extensive kennels, bred the dogs, and showed them nationally. Her dogs won many championships, and her kennels remained active until the 1950's. This series includes subject files (American Kennel Club material, Deerhound Club information, extensive records of Mrs. Huntington's kennels, scrapbooks, and other material) and published material (magazine articles and clippings about deerhounds and publicity material relating to the kennels).
In the interests of space, throughout the inventory Mrs. Huntington is referred to as "AHH."
Arrangement of the Collection
All series are arranged alphabetically, with the sole exception of the photographs of exhibits; these are arranged chronologically.
Related Material
The finding aids file contains several family trees compiled by staff during processing. Although every effort has been made to confirm names, dates and relationships, the charts should not be regarded as definitive.
has the papers of numerous members of the Hyatt, Mayor and Beebe families; please see our complete collection list under each surname for these. See also the following collections:
Archer Milton Huntington Papers (Anna's husband)
Arabella Huntington Papers (Archer's mother)
Collis P. Huntington Papers (Archer's father)
Huntington Estate Papers
Syracuse University also owns artwork by Anna Hyatt Huntington; please contact the Syracuse University Art Galleries at suart.syr.edu for more information.
Subject and Genre Headings
Art -- Sculptors; Huntington, Anna Hyatt, 1876-1973.; Huntington, Archer M. (Archer Milton), 1870-1955.; Brookgreen Gardens.; Hispanic Society of America.; Mariners' Museum (Newport News, Va.); Animal sculptors -- United States.; Animals in art.; Art -- Collectors and collecting.; Art, American.; Art, American -- 20th century.; Art museums.; Art patronage.; Bronze sculpture, American.; Scottish deerhound.; Dog breeders.; Endowments.; Equestrian statues.; Hispanists, United States.; Monuments.; Public art.; Public sculpture.; Sculptors -- United States.; Sculpture, American -- 20th century.; Sculpture gardens.; Upper class -- United States.; Women -- Biography.; Women and animals.; Women art patrons.; Women artists -- United States.; Women philanthropists.; Women sculptors -- United States.; United States -- Social life and customs -- 20th century.; 16mm (photographic film size); Address books.; Annual reports.; Articles.; Awards.; Bank statements.; Blueprints (reprographic copies); Calendars (documents); Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Diaries.; Exhibition catalogs.; Minutes (administrative records); Photographs.; Poems.; Posters.; Press releases.; Scrapbooks.; Slides (photographs); Studbooks.; Artists.; Sculptors.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Pellowe correspondence, gift of Kiersten Gawronski, 2021.
Inventory
- Art files
  - All-Transport Co. (Box 1)
  - Arden Gallery (Box 1)
  - A (Box 1)
  - [W.S.] Budworth and Sons (Box 1)
  - B (Box 1)
  - [Francis C.] Carr and Company, 1942-1958; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Comments and reviews of AHH's work (Box 1)
  - Contini, Attilio and Cesare (Box 1)
  - Contracts (Box 1)
  - Copyright information (Box 1)
  - C (Box 1)
  - Don Quixote, research material (Box 1)
  - Ettl Studios (Box 1)
  - Exhibits, See Photographs: Exhibits (Box 94 and Oversize 1) and Printed material: Exhibit catalogs and brochures (Boxes 109 and 110)
  - Flynn's Express (Box 1)
  - [J.J.] Gillespie Company (Box 2)
  - H (Box 2)
  - Insurance policies (Box 2)
  - I (Box 2)
  - Joan of Arc statue, clipping about horse used for model (Box 2)
  - [W.R.] Keating Company (Box 2)
  - Lists
    - Exhibitions by date (Box 2)
    - Exhibitions by work (Box 2)
    - Exhibitions, Studio Guild (Box 2)
    - Exhibitions, other (Box 2)
    - Sculpture gifts by institution (Box 2)
    - Sculpture gifts by state (Box 2)
    - Sculpture gifts by work, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Sculpture, miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - Marti statue, includes photograph of Marti (Box 2)
  - Modern Art Foundry Inc. (Box 2)
  - M (Box 3)
  - Notes (Box 3)
  - Orbit Shipping Company (Box 3)
  - O (Box 3)
  - Petsco, William (Box 3)
  - Pickett, Grace, 1938-1961; undated; 9 folders (Box 3)
  - Photographs, See Photographs: Artwork by AHH and Photographs: Exhibits
  - Roman Bronze Works, 1906; 1926-1967,; undated; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - R (Box 4)
  - Sofia Brothers (Box 4)
  - Speeches (Box 4)
  - Sybil Ludington statue, clippings, research notes (Box 4)
  - Studio Guild, 1937-1962; undated (Box 4)
  - "The Torchbearer" dedication, includes audiotape (Box 4)
  - T, V, W (Box 4)
  - Wallace, Claire (Box 4)
  - World's Fair, 1939; 1964 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
- Artwork (original)
  - By AHH
    - Medal, "Watering Hole" (Box 5)
      See also various medals in Photographs: Artwork by AHH.
    - Sketches (Box 5)
  - By others
    - Bregel [?], Peter, pen and ink drawings (Box 5)
    - Killman, Murray, Huntington relative; watercolor with letter on reverse (Box 5)
    - Mayor, Alfred Goldsborough, pen and ink sketches (Box 5)
    - Petrovic, M.V., pencil sketch (Box 5)
    - White, Elizabeth, prints (Box 5)
    - Unidentified (Box 5)
- Biographical material
  - Beebe family (Box 6)
  - Huntington, Alpheus Jr. (Box 6)
  - Huntington, Anna, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Huntington, Archer M. (Box 6)
  - Hyatt family (Box 6)
  - Mayor, Harriet, childhood reminiscences (Box 6)
  - Reynolds family (Box 6)
  - Vaughn, Daniel, assembled for DAR membership application (included) (Box 6)
- Correspondence-subject files
  - A (Box 7)
  - Abbate, Paolo S. (Box 7)
  - Abbe, Elfriede (Box 7)
  - Academy of American Poets (Box 7)
  - Accademie di Belle Arti (Box 7)
  - Accademie degli Euteleti (Box 7)
  - Adams, Cynthia DeFord, includes photograph (Box 7)
  - Adams, Edward A. (Box 7)
  - Adams, Herbert and Adeline, includes typescripts of poems (Box 7)
  - Adrian College (Box 7)
  - Agassiz, George Russell (Box 7)
  - Alba, Jacobo Stuart Fitz-James y Falco, ducque de, includes photo of his daughter, 1935 (Box 7)
  - Albert, Allen D., See Sheldon Swope Art Gallery (Box 54).
  - Alcohol Education, Foundation for (Box 7)
  - Alexander, Sara, See Brookgreen Gardens: General (Boxes 11-13).
  - Allen, Marion Boyd, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Alley, Reuben, Helene and Bobby (Box 7)
  - Allston, Susan Lowndes (Box 7)
  - Alva Belmont House, See Greenbie, Marjorie Latta Barstow (Box 33).
  - Amateis, Edmond R. (Box 7)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters
    - General, 1920-1954; 2 folders (Box 7)
      See also Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 15) and Johnson, Robert Underwood (Box 41).
    - Building contract (Box 7)
    - "Impressions and reminiscences of deceased members" (Box 8)
    - Minutes (Box 8)
    - Photographs (of building) (Box 8)
    - Resolution (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - American Antiquarian Society (Box 8)
  - American Artists Professional League (Box 8)
  - American Friends of Spain (Box 8)
  - American Geographical Society, 1920-1955; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1898-1955; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - American Numismatic Association (Box 9)
  - American Numismatic Society, 1929-1966; 6 folders (Box 9)
  - Anderson, Maxwell, includes photocopies of handwritten poems (Box 9)
  - Anderson Galleries (Box 9)
  - Angel, John (Box 9)
  - Angelis, Arnaldo de (Box 9)
  - Apel, Willi (Box 9)
  - Araquistain, Luis (Box 9)
  - Arciniegas, German (Box 9)
  - Arms, John Taylor (Box 9)
  - Art League of Manatee County (Bradenton, Fla.) (Box 9)
  - Art Times, See Boros, Billi (Box 11).
  - Artists' Fellowship, Inc. (Box 9)
  - Arts and Science Museum (Statesville, N.C.) (Box 9)
  - Asia Institute (Box 9)
  - Associazione Italo-Americana di Sicilia, See Hayward/Huntington/IBM Mediterranean exhibit (Box 35).
  - Atlanta Art Association (Box 9)
  - Atterbury, Grosvenor (Box 9)
  - Auslander, Joseph and Audrey, includes typescripts of poems (Box 9)
  - Avalos, Juan de, includes photographs of his sculpture (Box 9)
  - A-An (Box 9)
  - Ap-Az (Box 10)
  - Backer, Maurice (Box 10)
  - Bacon, Leonard, includes handwritten poem, "The Self-respecting Jaguar" (Box 10)
  - Bailey, Vernon Howe (Box 10)
  - Baillie, Robert A., 2 folders (Box 10)
    See also Brookgreen Gardens: General (Boxes 11-13).
  - Barnard, George Grey (Box 10)
  - Baldwin, Bob, Mr. and Mrs. (Box 10)
  - Barlow, Samuel (Box 10)
  - Barnard College (Box 10)
  - Barnard, George Grey (Box 10)
  - Barnard, Monroe Grey (Box 10)
  - Barto, Emily, includes typescript of poem, "The Wreck of the Emily Baxter" (Box 10)
  - Baruch, Bernard M. (Box 10)
  - Batista, Fulgencio (Box 10)
  - Beach, Chester (Box 10)
  - Beaux, Cecilia (Box 10)
  - Beebe, William (Box 10)
    See also New York Zoological Society (Box 49).
  - Bell, Aubrey FitzGerald (Box 10)
  - Bell, Enid (Box 10)
  - Benet-Espuny, Jose (Box 10)
    See also Memorabilia: Miscellaneous: Benet-Espuny, Jose (Oversize 3) for his original sketch of Stanerigg.
  - Benlliure, Mariano (Box 10)
  - Berenson, Bernard and Mary (Box 10)
  - Bernheim, Isaac Wolfe (Box 10)
  - Berry, Rose V.S. (Box 10)
  - Bertolli, Jean Tamburine (Box 10)
  - Billingsley, Logan, See National Hall of Fame for Famous American Indians (Box 48).
  - Bingham, Hiram, includes photographs of Bingham at Macchu Picchu (Box 10)
  - Birth, May E. (Box 10)
  - Blaine, Joan G. (Box 10)
  - Blair, — (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Blair, Henry W., 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Blasco-Ibanez, Vicente (Box 10)
  - Blashfield, Edwin Howland (Box 10)
  - Bliss, Charles M. (Box 11)
  - Bliss, Robert Woods (Box 11)
  - Blois, City of ("Diana") (Box 11)
  - [A.J.] Blosveren's Lamp Shop (Box 11)
  - Blueprints
    - Bus (for dogs) (Box 11)
    - Columbia Museum and Arts Center Sculpture Garden (Oversize 1)
    - El Cid plate (Box 11)
    - Fighting Stallions site, Southwest Texas State Teachers College (Oversize 18)
    - Huntington house, Redding, CT (Oversize 18)
    - Joan of Arc base (Box 11)
    - Kirtsis Park, Lincoln City, Oregon (Box 11)
    - Marti statue, base (Box 11)
    - Marti statue, New York City (Box 11)
    - Marti statue site (Oversize 18)
    - Raquette Lake (Box 11)
    - St. Gauden Galleries (Box 11)
    - Savings Bank of Danbury (Connecticut) (Box 11)
  - Boal, Sara and Arthur (Box 11)
  - Boardman, Nell (Box 11)
  - Boas, Franz, See American Museum of Natural History (Box 8).
  - Boehmer, Margaret Huntington (Box 11)
  - Bohland, Gustav (Box 11)
  - Bohnert, Herbert, Rosetta, and Mrs. William B. (Box 11)
  - Bonsor, George F. (Box 11)
  - Book of Knowledge Annual (Box 11)
  - Borglum, Gutzon (Box 11)
  - Borglum, Solon (Box 11)
  - Bori, Lucrezia (Box 11)
  - Boros, Billi (Box 11)
  - Boulton, Joseph, includes photo of his work (Box 11)
  - Bowman, Isaiah, includes photograph (Box 11)
    See also American Geographical Society (Box 8).
  - Bransom, Paul (Box 11)
  - Bregler, Charles (Box 11)
  - Brehm, James and Leslie (Box 11)
  - Briggs, Frederic R. (Box 11)
  - Brinckerhoff, A. F. (Box 11)
  - Brinton, Christian (Box 11)
  - Briscoe, Howard R. (Box 11)
  - Brockwell, Maurice Walter, See Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (Box 38).
  - Brookgreen Gardens
    - General
      See also Baillie, Robert A. (Box 10).
      - 1929-1939, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - 1940-1956, 14 folders (Box 12)
      - 1957-1968, 6 folders (Box 13)
      - Undated (Box 13)
    - Activity reports
      - 1959-1968, 4 folders (Box 13)
      - 1969-1973 (Box 14)
    - Annual reports (Box 14)
    - Articles about (Box 14)
    - Bank statements
      - Bank of New York (Box 14)
      - Guaranty Trust (Box 14)
      - J.P. Morgan and Co. (Box 14)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust (Box 14)
      - South Carolina National Bank (Box 14)
    - Blueprints (Box 14)
    - Bylaws (Box 14)
    - Cash statements (Box 14)
    - Clippings (Box 14)
    - Deed to No. 1 E. 89th (Box 14)
    - Financial statements, 1964; 1965 (Box 14)
    - Inventories (Box 14)
    - Legal and financial files, See Legal and financial files: Brookgreen (Box 61).
    - List of publications (Box 14)
    - Maps (Box 14)
    - Memorial resolution re: Archer Milton Huntington (Box 14)
    - Minutes
      - 1944, 1945, 1947 (Box 14)
      - 1956-1959 (Box 14)
      - 1960-1967 (Box 15)
    - Photographs, See: Memorabilia: Scrapbooks: Unidentified photos (possibly Brookgreen?) (Oversize 4) Photographs: Family property: Atalaya (Box 97) Photographs: Family property: Brookgreen Gardens (Box 98)
    - Poems about (Box 15)
    - Publications (Box 15)
    - Real estate booklet (Box 15)
    - Weekly reports (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous oversize (Oversize 2)
  - Brown, Barrett (Box 15)
  - Brown, Henry Collins (Box 15)
  - Brown, Sophie (Box 15)
  - Buba, Joy Flinsch (Box 15)
  - Buiza, D. Luis Toro (Box 15)
  - Bull, Henry D. (Box 15)
  - Bulloch, Hugh and Marie, See Academy of American Poets (Box 7).
  - Bumpus, Hermon Carey, See American Museum of Natural History (Box 8).
  - Burgos (Spain) (Box 15)
  - Burke, Marie Louise (Box 15)
  - Burlingame, Sheila (Box 15)
  - Burnham, Lee (Box 15)
  - Burns, Virginia (Box 15)
  - Burr Artists, See Lee, Eleanor Gay (Box 42).
  - Burr Galleries (Box 15)
  - Burton, E. Milby, See Charleston Museum (Box 16).
  - Bush, Prescott (Box 15)
  - Bushee, Alice Huntington (Box 15)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1921-1947; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Ba-Be (Box 15)
  - Bi-By (Box 16)
  - Calder, A. Stirling (Box 16)
  - California Palace of the Legion of Honor (San Francisco, Calif.) (Box 16)
  - Cantwell, Ida and Lee (Box 16)
  - Cardenas, Juan Francisco de (Box 16)
  - Carnegie Institute (Box 16)
  - Carolina Art Association (Box 16)
    See also Mechlin, Leila (Box 46).
  - Carpenter, Dolly (Box 16)
  - Carr, Ray M., includes original poem about AHH (Box 16)
  - Carr, Sally Swan (Box 16)
  - Carrizo, Juan Alfonso (Box 16)
  - Carter, Clara, See Coad, Clara Carter Hyatt (Box 16).
  - Carter, Granville W. (Box 16)
  - Caskel, Warner (Box 16)
  - Cassidy, Appolonia H. (Box 16)
  - Castro, Hector David (Box 16)
  - Caswell, Edward C. (Box 16)
  - Caturla, Maria Luisa (Box 16)
  - Caveney, Catherine (Box 16)
  - Cecere, Gaetano (Box 16)
  - Century Association (Box 16)
  - Chamber of Commerce (New York) (Box 16)
  - Chapin, Cornelia Van A. (Box 16)
  - Charleston Museum (Box 16)
  - Chase, Adelaide (Mrs. William Chester) (Box 16)